# **BRYNLEY MCDONALD**

# **CONTACT DETAILS**

Carlaw Park Student Residence 19 Nicholls Lane Auckland Central, Auckland 1010 New Zealand

Mobile: +64 22 414 6893 Website: https://zephire.nz

Github: <a href="https://github.com/ZephireNZ">https://github.com/ZephireNZ</a> Email: brynleymcdonald@gmail.com

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am currently studying a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, with the goals to enter the programming industry full time with past experience, a tertiary degree, and a true passion for the job I do.

I've been employed by businesses for development of websites and software giving me hands on experience in programming. In addition, working in a retail situation has given me a deeper understanding of the customer, and the ability to work within a team to meet goals and deadlines.

### SKILLS AND ABILITIES

#### **Technical Experience**

- In-production development experience designing, coding, and maintaining Java applications
- Over 2 years of study in Computer Science with a focus on back-ends, logic and computation
- Self-motivated to learn new platforms and concepts, through personal research or guided learning

## Ability to work well in a team

- Experience in a retail store, working as part of a team to meet the customer's needs, as well as those of the business
- 2 years working behind-the-scenes for school productions, with critical team roles

#### **Customer relations**

- Ability to express more complex ideas in a simple but comprehensive manner with customers
- Professional handling of various situations, including confused, frustrated or angered customers
- Finding the right solution

## **WORK HISTORY**

## **Jaycar Electronics**

Part-time from 2016 – Present

Sales Assistant

- Keeping store tidy, helping customers with a smile
- Learning many new products and concepts to help customers
- Balancing customer needs and business interests

#### **Dick Smith Electronics**

Part-time from 2014 - 2016

Sales Consultant / Manager

- Providing the customer with a complete solution for their needs
- Keeping current with technology trends
- Management of store during liquidation

Noirland Casual from 2012 – 2016

Development of 'plugin' software for a Minecraft server

- Planning of software outlined by client
- Creating that software to meet brief and specifications
- Maintaining and updating software

Studio 128 Casual from 2011 – 2013

Web Design and Systems Upkeep

- Development and design of business website
- Meeting with client to reach an outcome
- Upkeep of designed systems

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Auckland – BSc CompSci/LogiComp

2014 - Present

- A in COMPSCI314 Modern Data Communications
- A- in COMPSCI340 Operating Systems
- A- in COMPSCI210 Computer Systems
- A- in COMPSCI230 Software Construction
- B in COMPSCI220 Algorithms and Data Structures
- B in COMPSCI225 Discrete Structures in Mathematics and Computer Science
- A- in COMPSCI107 Computer Science Fundamentals
- B+ in MKTG151G Essential Marketing

#### REFERENCES

Available on Request

Curriculum Vitae – Brynley McDonald brynleymcdonald@gmail.com